Guide to the Robert Louis Wegryn photonegatives, 1955-1959.
Wegryn, Robert Louis photonegatives, 1955-1959
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert Louis Wegryn photonegatives, 1955-1959.
37-05-2192
Robert Louis Wegryn, 1937-
.5 cubic ft.
Photonegatives.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photographs taken for the Cornell Daily Sun, the Cornellian, and the Ithaca Journal of events in and around Ithaca. Subjects include parades and floats; fraternities, particularly Pi Kappa Alpha; and the 1958 riots around President Malott's house.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Wegryn was a phtographer and photo editor for the Cornell Daily Sun, 1955-1959.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photographs taken for the Cornell Daily Sun, the Cornellian, and the Ithaca Journal of events in and around Ithaca. Subjects include parades and floats; fraternities, particularly Pi Kappa Alpha; and the 1958 riots around President Malott's house.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wegryn, Robert Louis, 1937-; Cornell University--Riot, 1958.; Cornell University--Periodicals.; Cornell University. Pi Kappa Alpha.
Titles:
The Cornell Daily Sun.; Cornellian.; Ithaca Journal.
Subjects:
Student newspapers and periodicals.
Form and Genre Terms:
Negatives.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Accident (Box 1)
- Accident Mink (Girl got hit), Mar. 1957 (Box 1)
- Accident on Tower Road, Nov. 1957 (Box 1)
- Accident, Auto-Dean Cleary, Apr. 1957 (Box 1)
- Accident on Stewart, Apr. 1958 (Box 1)
- Adding Machine Co. (New Building), Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Annabel Taylor Hall (Box 1)
- Architecture Dome, 1956 (Box 1)
- Architecture and Studying (Box 1)
- Architecture Students, Sept. 1956 (Box 1)
- Architecture Exhibit of Longwood Redevelopment Project, Mar. 1958 (Box 1)
- Baseball (Box 1)
- Blood Drive, 1957 (Box 1)
- Big Red Band, 1956 (Box 1)
- Bond Issue Vote, May 1957 (Box 1)
- Bond Issue Fight, 1957 (Box 1)
- Bowling 300 (Box 1)
- Calypso Car IFC Weekend, Feb. 1957 (Box 1)
- Calumet (Box 1)
- Calumet, 1957 (Box 1)
- Calumet, 1957 (Box 1)
- Calumet, 1957 (Box 1)
- Camp Calumet (Box 1)
- Camp Calumet (Box 1)
- Camp Calumet, Scenes from (Box 1)
- Camp Calumet, Scenes from (Box 1)
- The Calumet Five (Box 1)
- Campbell (Band Director), May 11, 1957 (Box 1)
- Caveat Emptor (Box 1)
- Clinic Dedication, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Clinic-Psychological Research, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Clinic Truck, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Coffin-honored by faculty and alumni (Box 1)
- Community Center, South Side (Box 1)
- Construction, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Construction-Clinic, Engineering Bldg., Statler, Sept. 1956 (Box 1)
- Construction of Skating Rink, Sept. 1956 (Box 1)
- Construction of Skating Rink, Sept. 1956 (Box 1)
- Construction-Statler, New Engineering Quad, Crew, Vet School, Clinic, Sept. 1956 (Box 1)
- Crandel - Presentation of awards by faculty and alumni (Prof. Hollister presents), June 1958 (Box 1)
- Crew, 1956 (Box 1)
- Crew: Informal and Proctors, Sept. 1956 (Box 1)
- Crew on Spring Day, May 1957 (Box 1)
- Crew, Informal - Stanford and Boys Practicing, May 1957 (Box 1)
- Crew-IRA, June 1958 (Box 1)
- Cross-Country Skiing (Box 1)
- Dancing (Box 1)
- Debate, 1956 (Box 1)
- Debate, 1956 (Box 1)
- Defert, Apr. 1957 (Box 1)
- Defert, Apr. 1957 (Box 1)
- Defert, Apr. 1957 (Box 1)
- Defert, Clan and Mayor, 1957 (Box 1)
- Dorm Waterfight, 1955 (Box 1)
- Drama Club (CDC) (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC, 1956 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC - Spring Weekend, 1957 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC: The Tavern, Oct. 1957 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC, Nov. 1957 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC, 1958 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC: Fall Weekend, Nov. 1957 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC - Backstage, Apr. 18, 1958 (Box 1)
- Drama Club CDC - "A Different Drummer?", May 17, 1958 (Box 1)
- Duel - Fall Week, 1958 (Box 1)
- Duel - Fall Weekend, 1958 (Box 1)
- Dinklager, Dr. Kenneth Clinical Psycologist (Box 1)
- Fall Weekend Dance, 1956 (Box 1)
- Fall Weekend Dance and Queen, 1956 (Box 1)
- Fall Weekend Decoration, 1956 (Box 1)
- Family (Box 1)
- Family - Christmas, 1955 (Box 1)
- Family - Bobbie, IFC, 1957 (Box 1)
- Family - Crypt, 1957 (Box 1)
- Family N.H. - Christmas, 1957 (Box 1)
- Family - Heidi and Lena, 1957 (Box 1)
- Family - Tara and Heidi, Jan. 1957 (Box 1)
- Family - Mrs. Marroquin, Aug. 1958 (Box 1)
- Fashion Supplement, Spet. 1957 (Box 1)
- Fashion, 1958 (Box 1)
- Fire - Elize, Feb. 1957 (Box 1)
- Fire on Someone's Porch, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Fire - Cornell Barn, Oct. 1957 (Box 1)
- Fire - Barn across Lake, May 8, 1957 (Box 1)
- Fire - Chi Phi, Sept. 1958 (Box 1)
- Fire - ZBT, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Fire - ZBT, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Fire - ZBT, Sept. 1957 (Box 1)
- Football, Cornell (Box 1)
- Football (Box 1)
- Football (misc.) (Box 1)
- Football (misc.) (Box 1)
- Football (misc.) (Box 1)
- Football Sidelines (Box 1)
- Football Stadium (Box 1)
- Penn (Football) (Box 1)
- Penn Football (Box 1)
- Football: Syracuse (Box 1)
- Football, 1956 (Box 1)
- Football: Penn, 1956 (Box 1)
- Football Sidelines, 1956 (Box 1)
- Football Sidelines, 1956 (Box 1)
- Football Sidelines - Gold Posts Down, 1956 (Box 1)
- Football Locker and Sidelines, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
- Football: Brown, 1957 (Box 1)
- Football: Brown, 1957 (Box 1)
- Football: Colgate, 1957 (Box 1)
- Football: Colgate, 1957 (Box 1)
- Football: Columbia, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Harvard, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Harvard, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Harvard, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Penn, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Princeton, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Syracuse, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Syracuse, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football: Yale, 1957 (Box 2)
- Football, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Colgate, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Colgate, Sept. 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: "Colgate" dumped over girl, publicity committee for football, Sept. 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Dartmouth, Nov. 15, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Harvard, Sept. 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Harvard (wins), Sept. 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Penn, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Penn, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Princeton, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Syracuse, 1958 (Box 2)
- Football: Syracuse (Box 2)
- Formal, A Couple Dressed for a (Box 2)
- Fraternity Rushing, 1959 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, 1956 (Box 2)
- Frosh Camp, Sept. 1957 (Box 2)
- Frosh Elections, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Election of Queen, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Elections - Queen and Council, 1955 (Box 2)
- Frosh Open House, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Frosh Open House, Balch II, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Frosh Open House, Balch II, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Frosh Orientation, Balch, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Frosh Orientation, Convocation, Rally (Box 2)
- Frosh Orientation, Picnic Arriving, 1956 (Box 2)
- Goldfish Swallowing Darry Turgean by A.D. White Statue, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Graduation (Box 2)
- Graduation: Processions and Services, 1957 (Box 2)
- Graduation, June 1958 (Box 2)
- Graduation, June 1958 (Box 2)
- Graduation, June 1958 (Box 2)
- Graduation, June 1958 (Box 2)
- Garden - Big Red Barn (Box 2)
- Grand Prix, Sept. 1958 (Box 2)
- Hack-Camp, Chick, Bobbie (Box 2)
- Hack, Hagenbault and Pat (Box 2)
- Hack, Sneidi (Box 2)
- Hack, Barston, 1955 (Box 2)
- Hack, Spindler, 1955 (Box 2)
- Hack, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hack, Pat and Barbara at Party, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hack, Pat Poderta, Apr. 1956 (Box 2)
- Hack, Robinson, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hack, Everett, 1957 (Box 2)
- Hack, Everett, Sept. 1957 (Box 2)
- Hack, Nohmias, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hall, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hammondsport, 1956 (Box 2)
- Hammondsport, Sept. 1958 (Box 2)
- Harriman, Oct. 4, 1957 (Box 2)
- Hats of Spindler (Box 2)
- HEPS, 1956 (Box 2)
- HEPS - Hall Receives Award for Outstanding Athlete, 1956 (Box 2)
- HEPS - Kwapp High Jump, 1956 (Box 2)
- HiFi Equipment, Apr. 7, 1958 (Box 2)
- Hollister Award (Box 2)
- Hunt (Prof.), 1956 (Box 2)
- IFC Weekend Band, 1957 (Box 2)
- IFC Weekend Band, 1957 (Box 2)
- IFC Weekend Band, 1957 (Box 2)
- IFC - Men Talking to Frosh before Rushing, Feb. 1957 (Box 2)
- IFC - Meeting on Social Code, Dec. 1957 (Box 2)
- IGA (International Geophysical Year Activity) (Box 2)
- IGA (Box 2)
- International Exhibition by Frosh Class, Feb. 1957 (Box 2)
- Ithaca, Parks in (Box 2)
- Ithaca, Old Movies of (Ithaca College) (Box 2)
- Ivy Room, 1956 (Box 2)
- Ivy Room, 1956 (Box 2)
- Ivy Room, Nov. 1956 (Box 2)
- Ivy Room, Nov. 1957 (Box 2)
- Library, Nov. 1956 (Box 2)
- Maharaja - Arrives at Airport, Feb. 1958 (Box 2)
- "Making Out," Pi Kappa Alpha - Spring Day, 1956 (Box 2)
- "Making Out", 1957 (Box 2)
- "Making Out", 1957 (Box 2)
- "Making Out", 1957 (Box 2)
- Mallot, Tea and Dedication of Memorial House (Box 2)
- Mohawk Airlines, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Mohawk Airlines, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Monkey (Box 2)
- Mug: Wrestler (Box 2)
- Nabokov, V., Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Newman Chapel (Box 2)
- Newman Meeting, 1955 (Box 2)
- Newman - Spaghetti Dinner, 1955 (Box 2)
- Newman Smorg., 1955 (Box 2)
- Newman, Mrs. Cornelius, 1956 (Box 2)
- Newman (Officero), Apr. 1956 (Box 2)
- Newman Christmas Party, 1956 (Box 2)
- Newman Club, May 1958 (Box 2)
- Nobel Prize Winner in Physics, Mr. Lee, 1957 (Box 2)
- Nobel Prize Winner in Physics, Mr. Lee, 1957 (Box 2)
- Nursery for Faculty Children, 1956 (Box 2)
- Octagon, May 1958 (Box 2)
- Old Gym (Girl's Gym), Apr. 1957 (Box 2)
- Pan Hellenic Picnic, May 1957 (Box 2)
- Pan Hellenic Picnic, May 1957 (Box 2)
- Panel in Olin (Konyitz), Apr. 29, 1957 (Box 2)
- Panel in Olin M., Apr. 29, 1957 (Box 2)
- Party (Box 2)
- Party, Sept. 1956 (Box 2)
- Party Vaid (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Exchange Dinner (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Exchange Dinner with Sigma Kappa, Oct. 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Initiation, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Initiation, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Initiation, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Initiation, June 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Party (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Party, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Party, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Party, Nov. 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Party, Nov. 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Pledges, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Sports, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Sports, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Football, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Spring Weekend Float, 1957 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Pledge, 1959 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Grand President Visit, Feb. 1958 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - New Bar, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - New Bar, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - March, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Pledges, May 1957 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Sports, 1956 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Rushing (Spring), 1958 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Spring Day Float, 1958 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha, 1958 (Box 2)
- Pi Kappa Alpha, Mar. 2, 1958 (Box 3)
- Pi Kappa Alpha, Dec. 1957 (Box 3)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Exchange Dinner (Box 3)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Spring Day, 1956 (Box 3)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Spring Day, 1956 (Box 3)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Initiation, 1956 (Box 3)
- Pi Kappa Alpha - Initiation (Box 3)
- Polo, Apr. 1956 (Box 3)
- Project Status, Sept. 1957 (Box 3)
- Rally, 1955 (Box 3)
- Rally, 1955 (Box 3)
- Ratcoski, Apr. 1958 (Box 3)
- Recording Session, June 1956 (Box 3)
- Registration, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- Registration, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- Registration, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- Registration, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- Reunion, 1956 (Box 3)
- Reunion, June 1958 (Box 3)
- Reunion, June 1958 (Box 3)
- Reunion - President Mallot at Reunion Rally, June 1958 (Box 3)
- Riot (Box 3)
- Roelofs, Professor Howard Mark, 1957 (Box 3)
- Roelofs, Professor Howard Mark, 1957 (Box 3)
- ROTC, May 1957 (Box 3)
- ROTC - President Review, May 1957 (Box 3)
- ROTC, May 1957 (Box 3)
- ROTC - The Big Picture, Oct. 1957 (Box 3)
- ROTC - The Big Picture, Oct. 1957 (Box 3)
- Rushing, 1959 (Box 3)
- Sacrilegious, Apr. 1956 (Box 3)
- Sandy, Apr. 1958 (Box 3)
- Savages, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Savages, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Savages, Oct. 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Savages, Oct. 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Scenery (Box 3)
- Scenes (Box 3)
- Scenes (Box 3)
- Scenes (Box 3)
- Scenes (Box 3)
- Scenes (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, 1956 (Box 3)
- Scenes, Distant Scenes of Campus (Box 3)
- : Barbara and Lola - White Statue, Libe Slope (Box 3)
- Taughannock (Winter), 1957 (Box 3)
- Scenes: U Halls (Box 3)
- Sigma Kappa, Nov. 1957 (Box 3)
- Soccer - Penn (Wegryn) (Box 3)
- Soccer - Princeton, 1957 (Box 3)
- Soccer - Princeton, 1957 (Box 3)
- Sorority (Box 3)
- Sorority - Rushing, Feb. 1957 (Box 3)
- Sorority - Rushing, 1959 (Box 3)
- Sorority - Rushing by Men, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sorority - Rushing by Men, Feb. 1956 (Box 3)
- Sport Shop (Box 3)
- Spring Day, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Carnival, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Carnival, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day: Concert, Dance, Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Concert, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Concert, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Concert, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Dance, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Dance, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Dance, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats, 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats (Winter), 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Day Floats (Winter), 1956 (Box 3)
- Spring Weekend Dance, May 1957 (Box 3)
- Sputnic, Oct. 1957 (Box 3)
- Student Agencies (Box 3)
- Student Agencies, Sept. 1957 (Box 3)
- Student Agencies, Sept. 1958 (Box 3)
- Student Council (Box 3)
- Student Council Election, Apr. 1956 (Box 3)
- Student Council Mugs, 1957 (Box 3)
- Sun, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun, Sept. 1957 (Box 3)
- Sun: Editor-in-Chief, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Sun: Editor-in-Chief, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Sun: Editor on a Date at the Octagon (Box 3)
- Sun Banquet, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Sun - Buisness Board, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun: Bell and Ryan, June 1958 (Box 3)
- Sun for Campus - Spring Pictures, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun - Cornellian, 1958 (Box 3)
- Sun - Cornellian, 1958 (Box 3)
- Sun - Kirk and Steph, 1957 (Box 3)
- Sun - Photography, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun - Photography, 1956 (Box 3)
- Sun - The Press Crew, June 1958 (Box 3)
- Sun Sign-Ups - Girls Sign Up for Sun at Registration, Sept. 1958 (Box 3)
- Sun - Truck, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- Swim Meet, 1956 (Box 3)
- Tennis - Spring Practice, 1956 (Box 3)
- Thai Dancers, 1955 (Box 3)
- Vet. School (New), May 1957 (Box 3)
- Waiters, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- Waiters, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- WSH Info Desk, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- WSH Info Desk, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- WSH Info Desk, Sept. 1956 (Box 3)
- WSH Reading Room, Sept. 1957 (Box 3)
- WSH Ticket Window, 1957 (Box 3)
- WVBR - at Dance in Studio (Box 3)
- WVBR, June 1956 (Box 3)
- WVBR - Helicopter Help Brings Supplies, 1958 (Box 3)
- X-Ray (Box 3)
- YASNY, You Ain't Seen Nothing Yet, student organization that decorated Barton Hall for the big-band fall and spring weekend dances., May 6, 1956 (Box 3)
- YASNY, May 6, 1956 (Box 3)
- YASNY (Fall), 1956 (Box 3)
- YASNY, Nov. 1956 (Box 3)